<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Matt Maciejewski</title>
    <link>https://www.mmaciejewski.com/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Matt Maciejewski</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://www.mmaciejewski.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>https://www.mmaciejewski.com/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.mmaciejewski.com/about/</guid>
      <description>I grew up in Colorado, moving to Pittsburgh to attend Carnegie Mellon University for my undergraduate degree, before moving to Baltimore to begin my graduate education at Johns Hopkins University.
I spend a lot of my time biking around, occasionally taking pictures. While I do enjoy nature a lot, I am particularly into urban environments. Some of my photos can be found on my Instagram here.
I am a big fan of hockey, following both the Colorado Avalanche and Pittsburgh Penguins, and even play the game myself (albeit very poorly).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Publications</title>
      <link>https://www.mmaciejewski.com/publications/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.mmaciejewski.com/publications/</guid>
      <description>2021 M. Maciejewski, S. Watanabe, S. Khudanpur. Speaker Verification-Based Evaluation of Single-Channel Speech Separation. Interspeech (in review). 2021
M. Maciejewski, J. Shi, S. Watanabe, S. Khudanpur. A Dilemma of Ground Truth in Noisy Speech Separation and an Approach to Lessen the Impact of Imperfect Training Data. Computer Speech and Language (in review). 2021
M. Maciejewski, J. Shi, S. Watanabe, S. Khudanpur. Training Noisy Single-Channel Speech Separation With Noisy Oracle Sources: A Large Gap and A Small Step.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
